My favorite food? Hmm. Strawberries, I guess.
I see. You have cute tastes, Miss Iona.
Hate to say I told you so, but Akira's down in the rankings again.
On top of that, she's been ditching work lately. She's really not worth it anymore.
Eh, her style doesn't really match her magazine anyway. Kind of their class, you know?
So what should we do about the front page model for the next issue?
What do you think? Drop Akira and go with Yuko?
Well, that's just lovely. I wish they'd have their little business talk somewhere else.
I like them with some milk and just a pinch of sugar. Is that weird?
Oh, oh, right. Strawberries. Sorry.
I always take the backside of my fork and smash them to bits.
Just so we're clear, I'm gonna make you apologize.
Open!
Oh, right?
You know what?
If you don't have the idea, we must move on like P есть it.
führen
it
I'm home.
My gosh.
What happened, Heatwe?
You're soaked to the bone.
Your friends didn't come with you?
Did they go home?
Anyway, dry yourself off before...
Heatwe?
Looks like I'm up first.
Aki-laki!
We're gonna school this scrub, Piraluck.
And don't go easy on her just because she's a noob.
Is it okay?
What?
Tama will fight to win this.
Of course.
I'll draw, drop a card in the inner zone,
have Piraluck grow,
and now say hello to Sky Cat.
Tama, let's grow!
I summon Kukuri and Monia!
You gotta tell your Elric to lay off the coffee.
It's weird.
I've never felt like this.
But battling Akuma is awful.
It's painful.
It is painful, but...
I love it!
What the hell?
No fair!
I thought she was supposed to be a newbie!
You are correct.
Though she's new to the game,
she takes battle quite seriously.
Huh?
This is talent.
She has a gift.
You trying to tell me something?
Why don't you turn around and say it to my face?
Huh?
You know what?
Screw you!
I don't even care anymore!
You just keep your mouth shut and do what I tell you!
Got it?
Let's get this crap over with quick!
Arts!
Time for Peeping Analyze!
Aw, poor Roo Roo.
Now I get to pick a card level,
then all the ones in your hand go bye-bye.
And since you dumb rookies love to play by the book,
there's only one answer.
Level four!
Huh?
It would seem you missed.
Ugh!
Who cares?
I don't need you to tell me that!
Why don't you do something useful
and figure out a wish for me instead?
My wish?
Here it comes!
Try not to flip out and wet yourself
when I see your dirty little secret!
Hurry it up, Piraluck!
I haven't had my dose of butthurt babies today!
There's nothing.
Huh?
What's your deal?
You Elrigs can't, like, malfunction, can you?
She has...
no wish.
Yeah, she's right.
I admit it.
I don't have a wish yet.
Huh!
What?
Let me get this straight.
You're battling as a selector,
but you have nothing you want to fight for?
That is, like, so messed up!
What are you, a sociopath or something?
All the selectors are, like,
do or die when it comes to their wishes!
And you're just crapping all over that
so you can have fun?
That is sick, yo. Sick!
Participating as a selector
without having a wish
is more than just wrong.
It's blasphemy.
I don't care what you say.
Huh?
Just means I have nothing to lose.
So you can't scare me!
Argora!
Toma!
What the hell is wrong with you?
You just said you don't have a wish.
So tell me.
Why the hell are you trying to stomp all over mine?
No, that's not why I did this.
I just wanted you to...
Don't give me that crap!
You just wanted to see me suffer, didn't you?
And I bet you enjoyed it!
Hold on a sec!
Let's stop.
Met with Ruko and Yuzuki.
Played Wii Cross at the library.
On our way back, we bought stuffed dumplings.
Ruko... and... Yuzuki...
Ichui!
What happened?
The words are disappearing!
What?
My notes!
Everything I wrote is just fading away!
I don't know why!
I can't remember!
Ichui.
Is Akira late again?
Yonah, have you heard from her?
Not today.
You know what? Forget it. I don't even care anymore.
Right? She's off the cover for next issue. Good riddance.
Better yet, why don't we just drop her for a while?
Sounds good.
Good.
Yonah.
You have the scent of battle on you. Or the stink of defeat, at least.
That reminds me.
Do you remember that poor girl who battled Yonah a while back?
That was her second battle. And her second defeat.
In other words, she was one loss away from bidding farewell to her wish.
Knowing that she was backed into a corner, you approached her.
And you sweet-talked her into another battle with a free win as bait.
And as she sat there struggling to breathe, suffering from the illness that ravaged her body,
you betrayed her. You crushed a dying girl for your own gain.
And it wasn't just her wish, but her very life that you snatched away from her.
What does it matter to you? I can run my battles however the hell I want, can't I? Can't I?
Yes, you certainly can. Though I do have to question the effectiveness of your little method,
since you lost so badly to the next girl Yonah beat.
That's why you stopped feeding off Yonah's scraps, isn't it?
And why you started picking on the rookie selectors instead.
Tell me how that worked out for you again?
Yet another loss. Pathetic.
I don't want your filthy hands disgracing any more selector battles.
Screw you!
Your wish is to see Yonah's life ruined, right?
I know you want to beat her.
So why don't you challenge her to a battle already? Why do you avoid it when she's right here?
I told you! I can battle however the hell I want to!
And either way, when I get my wish, you're going down!
Thank you very much.
Huh?
Oh, looks like Yuko's here for the shoot.
Are you kidding? But I thought me and Yonah were doing the cover today.
You don't have a shoot today. Sorry.
Huh? What?
While you were so occupied looking for rookie selectors to pick on,
you seem to have lost your coveted position as a model.
Aw, are you gonna cry?
You tried too hard to ruin Yonah's career,
and ended up ruining your own.
I don't want to keep them waiting.
Goodbye, loser.
I don't care about my career, or my life, or anything as long as I can ruin yours!
I'll tear you apart with my own two hands if I have to, you bitch!
Time to put her out of her misery.
It doesn't seem like you have a fever, but you're still not feeling well?
No. My head feels like it's gonna explode.
I see. Well, I'll call the school for you and tell them what's wrong.
You just lay there and take it easy, all right?
Now I'm making Grandma worry again.
Ruuu!
You! And I bet you enjoyed it!
Why do I like battles so much?
Why do I keep wanting to have them?
I know all the horrible things that'll happen if I continue playing.
But still, I can't stop!
You don't have to cry, Ruu!
You know what?
It makes Thomas so happy to see you have fun battling!
So don't be sad!
We can have lots of battles and-
No, stop it!
Please, Ruu!
Hey, Kazuki. You aren't too busy today, are you?
Yeah, let's hang.
Okay, sounds good.
Didn't think it'd say yes.
Cool, we can grab some grub.
If you like curry, I know a place.
Let's go!
Can we talk for a sec?
Nothing personal, but you and Kazuki are kind of leaving a bad impression on people.
What?
Like the way you two always hang out is bordering on creepy.
Geez, could you be any more blunt?
Anyway, don't look so upset. We're not teasing. We're actually really worried.
You're worried?
We've been hearing all those awful rumors about you two, so we came to give you some advice.
Do you think I'm stupid? What's it matter to you?
All right, fine. I'm actually worried about Kazuki. You, I couldn't care less about.
When I see you stalking him all day, it just makes me feel sorry for him.
Yeah, it's awkward. Maybe you don't realize it, but Kazuki's actually a pretty popular guy.
But now there's all these weird rumors because you...
Geez, nice attitude.
Guess what they say about them is true. Ew.
Now, now.
Damn it.
Yuzuki.
Don't talk to me!
What's wrong with them? Everyone's so stupid. They're the creepy ones, not me.
Howdy-do!
Ugh! I knew it! You're a selector, aren't you?
Yay! I finally met one! I'm the awesomest!
Ugh, selectors are so hard to find!
Oh, by the way, my name's Chiori. So, can we have a battle already? Pretty, pretty, please?
Listen, kid. Here's a little secret.
Ooh!
If you lose three selector battles, something unspeakably terrible happens to you.
Yuzuki.
Duh! I already knew that!
Heh! It's all written down right here!
Huh? A novel? Of Wecross?
Yep! So yeah, after your third loss, the magical Wecross factors inside your body go crazy and blow up like a hot air balloon!
Until kaboom! Guts flying everywhere!
Pretty scary!
Wait, that's not...
That's why selectors are so cool, right? They put their lives on the line to fight for their wishes!
Uh-huh.
Huh?
Hey, sorry. My girl here's a little soft in the head, you see?
Ugh! Eldora! She'll see how hard my head is when we battle!
Now, back to what I was saying before! I'm offering my commemorative first battle to you, Miss Selector on the playground!
I don't know.
Oh, stop it! You're too much, Kazuki!
It's not that big a deal.
You don't have to go home yet, do you?
Uh, no. I guess not.
Oh, good. There's still a bunch of stuff I need to ask you.
Come on, let's battle! Please, for me!
Fine.
Yuzuki!
Let's do this.
Yay! Finally!
It's battle time!
Hey, sweetie, I've got to step out for a bit. Try to take it easy, okay?
It's strange. I feel like I've been searching for something, but I can't remember what it is.
I just know that if I can't have it, nothing matters. And there's no reason to be alive anymore.
The bitter, bitter taste has defeat!
Yep, she's strong. Way stronger than you, Chiori. Sorry about that. Bet that was a waste of your time, huh?
You're so rude! Learn the rules. In our first fight, the heroine has to lose, okay?
Yeah, I'll be sure to write that one down.
Oh, here, give this a read. It's good. We'll meet again for sure, right?
Fairly well, selector!
Yup!
You alright?
Well, I finally won.
Yes.
All it takes are three losses, and my wish is gone forever.
But there's no telling how many times I have to win if I want it to come true.
Isn't that the way it works?
Only when the conditions are met.
The conditions, huh? That's kind of cryptic, don't you think?
I'm sure you'll tell me after it's too late.
All I've thought about is winning, but now I wonder what would happen if my wish was corrupted.
Maybe Kazuki would drift away from me?
No, it has to be worse than that.
I bet he would end up hating me, and I'd never see him again for the rest of my life.
He was with that girl. I wonder where they went.
Stop it.
Maybe they went to Momoka's place to pick out cards.
I think his friends are still new to the game.
That used to be our thing we did together, you know?
Yuzuki, listen to me.
Then maybe they'll go to a movie.
Stop by the food court afterwards to try out their new decks.
Then they'll get a snack.
And exchange numbers.
Laugh and smile.
Walk home together.
Yuzuki!
I hate it.
If they're gonna take Kazuki away from me, I'd rather just die now and get it over with!
No matter how upset you may be, you should never say something like that.
You don't think I'm serious?
I hate you for lying to me!
But I know… I know I need you for my wish to come true.
I'm not stupid!
I know Akira made a fool of me, but I beat that new girl no problem!
If I still have a shot at becoming an eternal girl, then my wish can come true!
Kazuki can be mine forever, and he won't be taken away from me!
Listen!
I am your Elrig through thick and thin.
I will always follow you, wherever fate takes us.
When I was living with Mom, I don't think I asked for too much.
I wasn't spoiled.
She always wanted to be left alone, so I tried not to bother her, but…
I don't know what Ruko's thinking. There's something… scary about her.
I never knew how or why I was scaring my Mom, and that made me afraid too.
But I'm fine as long as I have Grandma and Ayumu with me, and I try not to ask for too much from them.
I don't want to scare anyone, or bother anyone, or hurt anyone ever again.
But now…
You know what? It makes Thomas so happy to see you have fun battling!
No! No, please!
Where do you get off acting like a victim?
You just wanted to see me suffer.
And I bet you enjoyed it, didn't you?
Roo?
Wake up, Roo.
There's a phone call for you.
I explained that you were asleep, but apparently it's something important.
What?
Oh…
Sorry to just call out of the blue. Do you like parfaits?
I probably should have asked before I ordered, but I hope it's okay.
Ah, thanks.
Hitae usually gets the kind with candied chestnuts. This one looks awfully good. I'll have to come back here with her sometime.
So what did you…
I looked through Hitae's phone. She had your number and Yuzuki's in her contacts.
Huh?
You must think I'm a horrible mother for snooping, but I also found this. Here.
Hold on. Is this the notebook she kept on WeCross?
You've seen it?
Uh, yes, ma'am.
Hitae can't read it anymore. She said that all the words were disappearing. She also tells me she doesn't remember you.
Huh!
Today, Ruko and Yuzuki had your number and Yuzuki's in her contacts.
Huh?
You must think I'm a horrible mother for snooping, but I also found this. Here.
Hold on. Is this the notebook she kept on WeCross?
You've seen it?
Uh, yes, ma'am.
Hitae can't read it anymore. She said that all the words were disappearing. She also tells me she doesn't remember you.
Huh?
Today, Ruko and Yuzuki and I bought a matching set of scrunchies. They both look really cute when they put them in their hair. They said I was cute, too. I'll have to take their word for it. I was already so happy, but having the chance to be together with them, sharing all of our fun and joy, it was just wonderful. Friendship truly is a beautiful thing.
She was so happy to make new friends. She wouldn't stop talking about you. I don't know what went wrong.
Ruko, please, if there's anything you can tell me about what happened, even if you had an argument or she got angry at you over something, I don't care.
I promise I'm not trying to blame you, but it seems like something just snapped and I need to know what caused it.
Ruko, tell me.
Ito, I lost three times. I was just having fun battling with my friends. We didn't know what would happen if we lost. I mean, our wish had already come true. We didn't know it would get corrupted like that.
Ruko, I don't... Please, just explain what this is about. Ruko, wait!
I feel so lost. Everything is wrong. I don't know what to do anymore. Help me!
We are let's see.
Ruko, hold me!
possess me.
Ruko…
Thank you.